<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="module1_name">Assign Mentor</string>
    <string name="module2_name">Join In</string>
    <string name="module3_name">Let Me In</string>
    <string name="module4_name">Study Buddy</string>
    <string name="module5_name">Tech Library</string>
    <string name="module6_name">Tech Park</string>
    <string name="module7_name">Tech Trade</string>
    <string name="module8_name">Tec Mind</string>
    <string name="module9_name">TeleTech</string>
    <string name="module10_name">UG</string>

    <string-array name="modules">
        <item name="skeletonActivity">skeletonActivity</item>
        <item name="techLibraryActivity">techLibraryActivity</item>
        
    </string-array>

    <string name="module1_short_description">This is module 1 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module2_short_description">This is module 2 <b>dynamic</b> description, announcements will appear here.</string>
    <string name="module3_short_description">This is module 3 <b>dynamic</b> description, announcements will appear here.</string>
    <string name="module4_short_description">This is module 4 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module5_short_description">This is module 5 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module6_short_description">This is module 6 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module7_short_description">This is module 7 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module8_short_description">This is module 8 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module9_short_description">This is module 9 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module10_short_description">This is module 10 description, it describes what the module does.</string>
    <string name="module1_long_description">This is module 1 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module2_long_description">This is module 2 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module3_long_description">This is module 3 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module4_long_description">This is module 4 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module5_long_description">This is module 5 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module6_long_description">This is module 6 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module7_long_description">This is module 7 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module8_long_description">This is module 8 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    <string name="module9_long_description">This is module 9 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
        <string name="module10_long_description">This is module 10 longer description, it more informative and detailed from the short description of the module.</string>
    
</resources>